<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>

    <record id="action_offer_letter_full" model="ir.actions.report">
        <field name="name">Offer Letter ( Full )</field>
        <field name="model">hr.applicant</field>
        <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
        <field name="report_name">hrms_changes.report_offer_letter_full</field>
        <field name="report_file">hrms_changes.report_offer_letter_full</field>
        <field name="print_report_name">'Offer Letter - %s' % (object.partner_name)</field>
        <field name="binding_model_id" ref="model_hr_applicant"/>
        <field name="binding_type">report</field>
    </record>
    <record id="action_offer_letter_basic" model="ir.actions.report">
        <field name="name">Offer Letter ( Basic )</field>
        <field name="model">hr.applicant</field>
        <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
        <field name="report_name">hrms_changes.report_offer_letter_basic</field>
        <field name="report_file">hrms_changes.report_offer_letter_basic</field>
        <field name="print_report_name">'Offer Letter - %s' % (object.partner_name)</field>
        <field name="binding_model_id" ref="model_hr_applicant"/>
        <field name="binding_type">report</field>
    </record>
    <template id="report_offer_letter_full">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                <t t-call="web.external_layout">
                    <div class="page" style="font-size:13px;">

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <p>
                            <strong>[Private &amp; Confidential]</strong>
                        </p>

                        <p style="text-align:right;">
                            <strong>Date:
                                <t class="mt-1" t-esc="o.emp_hire_date"/>
                            </strong>
                        </p>
                        <!-- Address -->
                        <p>
                            <strong>
                                Ref.No: I210055
                                <br/>
                                Mr.
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_name"/>
                                <br/>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_street"/>
                                <br/>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_street2"/>
                                <t class="mt-1" t-esc="o.emp_city"/>
                                <br/>

                                <t t-esc="o.emp_state_id"/>
                                -
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_zip"/>
                                <br/>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_country_id"/>
                            </strong>
                        </p>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <h6>Appointment Letter</h6>
                        </div>
                        <p>Dear<strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_name"/>,
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            We refer to your candidature and to our discussions. We are pleased to offer you an
                            appointment
                            in our organization. Welcome onboard as a VSTian!
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Your designation will be<strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_job"/>. Your base location will be
                            <strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_location"/>
                            unless notified otherwise.
                        </p>

                        <!-- 1 -->
                        <h6>1. Appointment</h6>
                        <p>
                            Your date of appointment is effective from the date of joining
                            <strong class="mt-1"
                                    t-esc="o.join_date"/>
                            . Please carefully
                            review this offer of
                            employment before agreeing to its terms by signing it. The offer outlines important
                            benefits,
                            terms, and conditions
                            related to your employment with Vriksham Soft Tech. Kindly send your acceptance of this
                            offer
                            via return email.
                            Your joining date may be extended based on your written request, subject to the sole
                            discretion
                            of the Company. The
                            Company reserves the right to extend your date of joining due to changes in business
                            requirements, at its sole
                            discretion. This offer will expire if the Company does not receive your written acceptance
                            of
                            this offer letter or if
                            you fail to join the company on the agreed-upon date. Please indicate your acceptance of
                            this
                            offer by signing below
                            and returning it to HR by email within 5 days.
                        </p>

                        <!-- 2 -->
                        <h6>2. Compensation</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) Your fixed base pay (FBP), on an annualized basis, will be INR
                                <strong class="mt-1" t-esc="o.emp_annualized_basis"/>
                                will be paid
                                in
                                accordance with
                                the Company’s regular payroll process and procedures during your employment. This amount
                                will be
                                subject to all applicable withholdings. Additionally, you are eligible to receive
                                variable
                                pay
                                of INR
                                <strong class="mt-1" t-esc="o.emp_variable_pay"/>
                                upon 100% achievement of your target goals, which will be pro-rated based on your start
                                date.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) The breakdown of your fixed base pays into basic salary, allowances, benefits, and
                                perquisites (collectively
                                referred to as “compensation” or “salary”) is provided in Annexure I to this letter. You
                                will be
                                governed by
                                the policies, rules, and procedures of the Company regarding such compensation. The
                                Company
                                reserves
                                the right to modify the structure, amount, eligibility, and terms of such compensation
                                at
                                its
                                discretion.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (c) Your compensation will be subject to periodic review in accordance with Company
                                policy.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (d) Changes to your compensation are discretionary and will be based on effective
                                performance,
                                results during
                                the period, and other relevant criteria. You understand that information regarding your
                                compensation is
                                strictly confidential, and therefore, we kindly request you to maintain confidentiality.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (e) Your compensation will be subject to deductions for all governmental and local
                                taxes,
                                contributions, etc., in
                                accordance with applicable laws, including taxes on the value of perquisites.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                        <!-- 3 -->
                        <h6>3. Probation</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                You will undergo a probationary period of six months starting from the date of your
                                appointment, which
                                the Company reserves the right to extend at its sole discretion. Confirmation of your
                                services at the end of
                                the probationary period will be provided by the Company in writing.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 4 -->
                        <h6>4. Working Hours</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>(a) Your standard working days are Monday to Friday. You may be scheduled to work shifts
                                in
                                accordance
                                with the Company’s shift policy and customer requirements.
                            </p>
                            <p>(b) The Company retains the right to request that you work beyond your normal working
                                hours,
                                as needed, to
                                fulfill your duties.
                            </p>
                            <p>(c) These entitlements shall cease upon the termination of your employment with VST. They
                                may
                                also cease if
                                you need to take a long-term personal leave of absence. Please consult with your HR team
                                for
                                further
                                details
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 5 -->
                        <h6>5. Responsibilities</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>(a) Considering your position and role within the company, it is imperative that you
                                perform
                                all responsibilities
                                effectively, diligently, and to the best of your ability. You are expected to devote
                                your
                                entire working time,
                                abilities, and efforts to these responsibilities, ensuring satisfactory results.
                            </p>
                            <p>(b) Throughout your employment, you are prohibited from engaging in any activities or
                                investments that
                                conflict with the interests of the Company. Additionally, you must refrain from
                                activities
                                that distract you
                                from performing your responsibilities properly and efficiently or interfere with your
                                ability to exercise
                                independent judgment in the best interests of the Company.
                            </p>
                            <p>(c) It is essential that you adhere to the Company’s policies, which are an integral part
                                of
                                your employment
                                terms. Therefore, you are required to understand the scope and purpose of these policies
                                and
                                to comply
                                with them accordingly. These policies are subject to periodic updates and modifications,
                                and
                                new policies
                                may be introduced as needed. The Company will inform you of any changes, and you will be
                                expected to
                                adhere to them.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 6 -->
                        <h6>6. Work Authorization</h6>

                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>(a) If you require an employment visa to work in India, this appointment will not take
                                effect
                                until you have
                                obtained the necessary employment visa. If granted, your employment will be subject to
                                the
                                terms outlined
                                in the visa issued by the Indian Government.
                            </p>
                            <p>(b) If your employment visa is not extended within the validity period of the initial
                                visa,
                                your employment will
                                automatically terminate on the last day of the initial visa period without further
                                notice.
                                You agree to
                                promptly inform the Company if your employment visa extension is not granted.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 7 -->
                        <h6>7. Confidential information, Nondisclosure Agreement, Conflict of Interest and
                            Non-competition
                            Agreement
                        </h6>

                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) VST expects that, during and after the term of your employment, you will not
                                disclose to
                                third parties,
                                utilize for your own benefit, or otherwise make use of any of VST trade secrets or other
                                confidential or
                                proprietary information concerning VST, except to the extent necessary to carry out your
                                obligations to
                                VST.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) Please sign and return the enclosed Confidential Information, Non-Disclosure,
                                Conflict
                                of Interest, and
                                Non-Competition Agreement. This agreement contains, among others, your promise not to
                                recruit any
                                employees of VST or its clients and contractors for a period of one year following the
                                termination of your
                                employment relationship with VST. Additionally, you agree not to compete with VST for a
                                period of six
                                months following the termination of your employment relationship with VST.
                            </p>

                            <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                            <p>
                                (c) By signing this letter, you represent that your acceptance of this offer and your
                                employment with VST does
                                not and will not violate or otherwise conflict with any other agreement to which you may
                                be
                                a party.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (d) You also agree not to undertake employment, whether full-time or part-time, as the
                                Director/Partner/Member/Employee of any other organization/entity engaged in any form of
                                business
                                activity without the consent of VST.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 8 -->
                        <h6>8. Intellectual Property</h6>

                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) You agree to promptly surrender, disclose, and assign upon demand to VST or its
                                successors, designers, or
                                assigns, any inventions, creations, computer programs, training materials, or other
                                works
                                that you may
                                develop or assist in developing during your employment with VST.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) You acknowledge that such inventions, creations, computer programs, training
                                materials,
                                or other works,
                                and all rights pertaining to them, are works for hire and the sole property of VST.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (c) You further agree to grant and relinquish all rights or interests you may have in
                                such
                                creations, inventions,
                                or works.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (d) Moreover, you authorize VST, on your behalf, to sign any necessary papers and to
                                take
                                any actions deemed
                                necessary or desirable by VST to secure rights relating to such inventions, creations,
                                computer programs,
                                training materials, or works, including but not limited to patents and copyrights in
                                India
                                or any foreign
                                countries.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (e) Additionally, you agree to perform, during or after your employment, any further
                                acts
                                that are reasonable
                                and necessary or desirable to transfer, perfect, or defend the Company's or its
                                designee's
                                ownership of the
                                Employee Works, as reasonably requested by the Company.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 9 -->
                        <h6>9. Non-Solicitation</h6>

                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) You agree that for a period of one year following the cessation of your employment
                                with
                                the Company, you
                                will not solicit, induce, or attempt to induce any employee of the Company, directly or
                                indirectly, to
                                terminate their employment with the Company and become self-employed or employed
                                elsewhere.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) You acknowledge that this restriction is necessary and reasonable for protecting the
                                Company’s business
                                interests.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 10 -->
                        <h6>10. Return of Company Property</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) All notes, records, books, documents, equipment, laptops, or parts of PCs belonging
                                to
                                the Company,
                                whether created by you or provided to you during your employment, and containing
                                confidential
                                information (as defined herein), shall always remain the property of the Company.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) These items must be promptly returned to the Company upon your cessation of
                                employment
                                or at any other
                                time upon the Company's request.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (c) Additionally, you agree to return any credit cards, identification cards, laptops,
                                or
                                other Company property
                                or equipment immediately upon termination of your employment.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 11 -->
                        <h6>11. Right of Set-Off</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                If you incur any debt to the Company or if any money is owed to the Company by you
                                (including
                                overpayments made to you) for any reason, including but not limited to unpaid card
                                expenses,
                                phone bills,
                                or misuse or misappropriation of the Company’s assets, the Company reserves the right to
                                set
                                off such
                                outstanding amount from any amount due and payable to you.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                        <!-- 12 -->
                        <h6>12. Notice of Change</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                Any updates to your personal information, such as residential address, marital status,
                                number of children,
                                and educational qualifications, must be provided to the Company in writing within 7
                                days.
                                Any notices
                                intended for you will be considered properly delivered if given to you personally or
                                sent by
                                post to your last
                                recorded address in the Company’s records.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 13 -->
                        <h6>13. Sensitive Personal Data or Information</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) You are informed that the Company collects your personal data for payroll, career
                                management processes,
                                administrative staff management, and work organization purposes.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) For further details regarding the processing of personal data by the Company, refer
                                to
                                the provided
                                information.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (c) You acknowledge that, in the course of your employment with the Company, you may
                                access
                                certain
                                information, including personal data as defined by applicable laws. This may include
                                details
                                such as name,
                                address, email address, identity number, or any other information that could directly or
                                indirectly identify
                                an employee, client, service provider, or any other individual whose personal data is
                                collected by the
                                Company.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (d) You agree to process personal data that you have access to during your employment
                                strictly in accordance
                                with the Company’s directives and solely for the purpose of fulfilling your work duties.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (e) You commit to maintaining the confidentiality and security of any data you always
                                access
                                and processing
                                the data in compliance with applicable laws and the Security Policies adopted by the
                                Company.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (f) You undertake not to utilize personal data for any purpose other than what is
                                necessary
                                to fulfill your
                                responsibilities as an employee of the Company.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- PAGE BREAK -->

                        <!-- 14 -->
                        <h6>14. Exclusivity / Prior Commitment</h6>

                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) You agree to work exclusively for the Company within the context of the defined
                                responsibilities and
                                refrain from accepting or engaging in any other paid or unpaid employment or consulting,
                                even
                                temporarily.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) You represent and warrant to the Company that:
                            </p>

                            <div style="margin-left:20px">
                                <p>
                                    (a) You are not subject to any covenants, agreements, or restrictions, including
                                    those
                                    arising from prior
                                    employments or independent contractor relationships, which would be breached by
                                    executing this
                                    Agreement or performing your duties herein.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (b) You will not bring onto the Company’s premises, use, or incorporate any
                                    unpublished
                                    documents or
                                    property belonging to past employers without their written consent.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (c) There is no court order or other authority disqualifying you for appointment
                                    under
                                    this agreement.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 15 -->
                        <h6>15. Jurisdiction</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) The jurisdiction regarding your current employment will exclusively lie with the
                                courts
                                in New Delhi,
                                which you undertake not to contest.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (b) The appointment will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of
                                India.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (c) This Agreement, including the referenced policies and other documents, constitutes
                                the
                                entire agreement
                                between you and the Company regarding the subject matter herein. It cannot be modified,
                                except as
                                expressly stated herein, without an amendment signed by both parties.
                            </p>

                            <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                            <p>
                                (d) If a court declares any provision void, that provision will be severed from this
                                Agreement, and the
                                remaining provisions shall remain fully enforceable.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 16 -->
                        <h6>16. Termination of Employment</h6>

                        <p>
                            You are entitled to receive from the Company and required to give the Company the following
                            period of notice, in
                            writing, to terminate your employment without cause, such notice, in each case, to expire as
                            stated below:
                        </p>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (i) During the probation period, either party may terminate this contract by giving
                                Thirty
                                days’ notice in
                                writing or payment in lieu of salary (net of provident fund contribution and gratuity).
                                However, the
                                Company reserves the right not to accept payment in lieu of notice and at its sole
                                discretion and
                                enforce the notice period.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                (ii) After your probation period, either party may terminate this contract by giving
                                Ninety
                                days’ notice in
                                writing or payment in lieu of salary (net of provident fund contribution and gratuity).
                                However, the
                                Company reserves the right not to accept payment in lieu of notice and at its sole
                                discretion and
                                enforce the notice period.
                            </p>
                            <div style="margin-left:20px">
                                <p>
                                    (a) In any event (unless mutually agreed in writing), your employment will
                                    automatically
                                    end upon
                                    reaching the Company’s retirement age. The retirement age for a full-time employee
                                    is 58
                                    years.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (b) Your employment is liable to be terminated immediately by the Company without
                                    prior
                                    notice if any
                                    information provided by you in your employment verification form or in connection
                                    with
                                    your appointment
                                    is found to be false, or if any material particulars are suppressed.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (c) Furthermore, the Company reserves the right to terminate your services without
                                    notice or salary in lieu
                                    thereof for misconduct, negligence of duty, disloyalty, dishonesty, indiscipline,
                                    disobedience, irregular
                                    attendance, prolonged absence from duty due to ill-health, infirmity, accident, or
                                    inefficiency compared to
                                    other employees.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (d) The Company may also terminate your employment immediately and without notice if
                                    you
                                    (i) commit a
                                    crime involving moral turpitude, theft, fraud, or deceit; (ii) engage in conduct
                                    that
                                    adversely affects the
                                    Company’s reputation; or (iii) exhibit conduct unbecoming of your position.
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (e) If you are absent without leave or remain absent beyond the granted or extended
                                    leave period, you shall
                                    be considered to have voluntarily terminated your employment without notice unless
                                    you:
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (f) Return to work within 3 days of the start of such absence; and
                                </p>
                                <p>
                                    (g) Provide a written explanation satisfactory to your manager regarding the
                                    absence.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 17 -->
                        <h6>17. Verification</h6>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                (a) This offer is contingent upon obtaining no adverse information during reference
                                checks
                                with your
                                previous employer(s), background check, and validation of the experience and educational
                                qualifications you have submitted.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- 18 -->
                        <h6>18. General</h6>
                        <p>
                            You agree that the provisions of this letter are severable. If any portion thereof is
                            declared
                            unenforceable, it shall not
                            affect the enforceability of all other provisions herein. The intent of the parties is that
                            if
                            any part of this letter
                            contains provisions deemed unreasonable, a court shall determine the terms of such agreement
                            or
                            enforce the terms
                            deemed reasonable.
                        </p>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                        <p>
                            By accepting this offer of employment, you affirm that you have not signed any agreements
                            with
                            prior employers, or
                            otherwise, that would restrict your ability to: (a) work for a competitor; (b) solicit
                            customers; (c) recruit employees;
                            or (d) perform the responsibilities of the position outlined in this offer letter. If you
                            discover any such agreements,
                            you must notify us immediately. You also affirm that you have not taken nor are in
                            possession of
                            any confidential
                            and/or proprietary information belonging to prior employers.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            You will be required to sign certain mandatory agreements, including but not limited to the
                            Confidentiality
                            Agreement, Intellectual Property Rights Agreement, and the Code of Business Ethics. Your
                            employment will be
                            governed by all rules and regulations, as amended from time to time. Additionally, the
                            Company
                            has various human
                            resources and administration policies and procedures, which may be subject to change at any
                            time
                            at the Company's
                            discretion. While these policies are not part of your contract of employment, you are
                            required
                            to comply with all
                            applicable policies.
                        </p>
                        <p>
                            We are pleased to welcome you to our Company and look forward to a mutually beneficial
                            association.
                        </p>

                        <br/>
                        <br/>

                        <p>With best wishes, Yours truly,</p>

                        <br/>
                        <br/>

                        <p>
                            <strong>For
                                <strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_company"/>
                            </strong>
                        </p>
                        <p>
                            <strong>
                                <strong t-esc="o.emp_hr_name"/>
                                <br/>HR Head
                            </strong>
                        </p>

                        <br/>
                        <br/>

                        <p>
                            I have carefully read and understood the terms and conditions mentioned above. I accept all
                            the
                            terms and conditions
                            of this offer of employment. I shall commence employment with effect from
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Date:
                            <br/>
                            <br/>
                            Place:
                            <br/>

                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">

                                    Name:
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">

                                    Signature:
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </p>

                        <!-- PAGE BREAK -->
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>

                        <!-- ANNEXURE -->
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <h6>Annexure I</h6>
                        </div>
                        <h6>Compensation Structure</h6>
                        <t t-esc="o.emp_calculation_table"/>

                        <br/>

                        <p>
                            At the time of joining, you are requested to bring the following documents in original,
                            along
                            with one
                            copy each:
                        </p>
                        <div style="margin-left:20px">
                            <p>
                                1) Certificates supporting your educational qualifications along with mark sheets:
                            </p>
                            <div style="margin-left:20px">
                                <p>
                                    (b) Std X Certificate and mark sheet
                                    <br/>
                                    (c) Std XII Certificate and mark sheet
                                    <br/>
                                    (d) Degree Certificate and Semester-wise / Year-wise mark sheets
                                    <br/>
                                    (e) Master’s Degree Certificate and Semester-wise / Year-wise mark sheets
                                    <br/>
                                    (f) Diploma /PG Diploma Certificate and Transcripts
                                    <br/>
                                    (g) Any other Certificates with supporting documents, if any
                                    <br/>
                                    (g) Any other Certificates with supporting documents, if any
                                </p>
                            </div>
                            <p>
                                2) Your relieving letter / Service Certificate from the last three employers
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                3) Acknowledged copy of our offer of appointment
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                4) 4-passport sized color photographs with white background
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                5) Valid pages of the Passport
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                6) Valid government ID proof for your current / permanent address
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                7) PAN Card
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                8) Please ensure to bring all the Certificates supporting your educational
                                qualifications
                                along with
                                mark sheets in original for verification purposes only.
                            </p>
                        </div>

                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>


    <template id="report_offer_letter_basic">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                <t t-call="web.external_layout">
                    <div class="page">

                        <!-- Title -->
                        <h3 class="text-center">
                            <b>OFFER LETTER</b>
                        </h3>

                        <br/>

                        <!-- Reference -->
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-6">

                                <strong>
                                    Ref.No: I210055
                                </strong>

                            </div>
                            <div class="col-6 text-end">
                                <strong class="mt-1" t-esc="o.emp_hire_date"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <!-- Address -->
                        <p class="mt-4">
                            <strong>
                                Mr.
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_name"/>
                            </strong>
                            <br/>
                            <span>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_street"/>
                            </span>
                            <br/>
                            <span>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_street2"/>
                                <t class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_city"/>
                            </span>
                            <br/>

                            <span>
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_state_id"/>
                                -
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_zip"/>,
                                <t t-esc="o.emp_country_id"/>
                            </span>
                        </p>

                        <br/>

                        <!-- Content -->
                        <p><strong>Dear</strong><strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_name"/>,
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            We refer to your candidature and to our discussions. We are pleased to offer you an
                            appointment with
                            our organization. Welcome onboard as a VSTian!
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Your designation will be<srong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_job"/>. Your base
                            location
                            will be
                            <strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_location"/>
                            unless notified
                            otherwise.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Your CTC will be
                            <strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_gross_amount"/>
                            <strong class="ms-1">/- Per Annum</strong>, the detailed Compensation package offered
                            to you are given in
                            Annexure A.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            The documentation necessary at the time of your joining is listed in Annexure B.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Your joining date is
                            <strong class="ms-1"
                                    t-esc="o.emp_join_date"/>
                            .
                            Please convey your acceptance of this offer within 3
                        </p>

                        <p>days of
                            receiving this offer.
                            You will be on 30 days of notice as per the company policy.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            We welcome you to
                            <t t-esc="o.emp_company"/>
                            and looking forward to a long and mutually rewarding
                            association with you.
                        </p>

                        <br/>
                        <br/>

                        <p>For<strong class="ms-1" t-esc="o.emp_company"/>,
                        </p>

                        <br/>
                        <br/>

                        <p>
                            <b>
                                <strong>Vinodhini D</strong>
                            </b>
                            <br/>
                            <strong>HR HEAD</strong>
                        </p>

                        <!-- Annexure A -->
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>

                        <h6 class="text-center">
                            <b>Annexure - A</b>
                        </h6>
                        <h4>Compensation Structure</h4>
                        <t t-esc="o.emp_calculation_table"/>

                        <!-- Annexure B -->
                        <h6 class="text-center mt-4">
                            <b>Annexure - B</b>
                        </h6>

                        <p>
                            At the time of joining, you are requested to bring the following documents in original,
                            along with
                            one copy each.
                        </p>

                        <ul>
                            <li>Certificates supporting your educational qualifications along with mark sheets</li>
                        </ul>
                        <ol style="margin-left: 50px;">
                            <li>Std X Certificate and mark sheet</li>
                            <li>Std XII Certificate and mark sheet</li>
                            <li>Degree Certificate and Semester-wise / Year-wise mark sheets</li>
                            <li>Master’s Degree Certificate and Semester-wise / Year-wise mark sheets</li>
                            <li>Diploma / PG Diploma Certificate and Transcripts</li>
                            <li>Any other Certificates with supporting documents, if any</li>
                        </ol>

                        <ul>
                            <li>Your latest salary slip / Salary Certificate</li>
                            <li>Your relieving letter / Service Certificate from the last three employers</li>
                            <li>Acknowledged copy of our offer of appointment</li>
                            <li>4 passport sized colour photographs with white background</li>
                            <li>Valid pages of the Passport</li>
                            <li>Valid government ID proof for your current / permanent address</li>
                            <li>PAN Card</li>
                        </ul>

                        <p>
                            Please bring all the Certificates supporting your educational qualifications along with mark
                            sheets
                            in original for verification only.
                        </p>

                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>